{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Which one of the following is NOT true about MVC",
            "options": [
                "Presentation of the data is separate from the storage of the data",
                "Reusability",
                "Model is a mediator between View and Controller",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "answer": "Model is a mediator between View and Controller"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of the software engineering best practices is to define the overall software architecture in early stage",
            "options": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "True"
        },
        {
            "question": "Controller in the MVC pattern is used to manage database.",
            "options": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "False"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of the following is true about the Layered Architecture Pattern",
            "options": [
                "The system is modular allowing layers to be replaced if needed",
                "Is less efficient than systems that allow for direct communication between all components",
                "Allows for multiple levels of security",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "answer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
            "question": "Server-Client pattern is a good choice when the load on a system needs to increase over time.",
            "options": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "True"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Pipe and Filter pattern is a good choice when an application requires manual intervention as part of the process.",
            "options": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "False"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is true about the Publisher-Subscriber Pattern?",
            "options": [
                "Data consumers can process data at a different pace than the data producers.",
                "Often experience performance degradation if one consumer is slower than the others.",
                "Is unaffected by unexpected surges in message traffic",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "answer": "Data consumers can process data at a different pace than the data producers."
        },
        {
            "question": "Microservices are a good choice if each system has different resource requirements since they can be scaled independently.",
            "options": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "True"
        },
        {
            "question": "Correct application of the Microservices pattern requires that each service can be deployed independently.",
            "options": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "True"
        },
        {
            "question": "The strangler facade allows a legacy system to be replaced without disrupting clients who are actively using the system.",
            "options": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "True"
        }

    ]
}